Finding Aid for Alumni Association (University of Michigan) records, 1845-2001
Bentley Historical Library
- Photographs, Circa 1869-1997
  - Michigan Alumnus Magazine files
    - Subjects
      - Student life
        - To, 1920 (Box 138)
        - 1920s (Box 138)
        - 1930s (Box 138)
        - 1940-1945 (Box 138)
        - 1945-1949 (Box 138)
        - 1950s (Box 138)
        - 1960s (Box 138)
        - Undated
          - circa 1920s-1930s (Box 138)
          - circa 1940s-1950s (Box 138)
        - In class (Box 138)
      - Summer Session (Box 138)
      - Swingout (Box 138)
      - Tablets and monuments (Box 138)
      - Tecumseh Health Study, 1959 (Box 138)
      - Television (Box 138)
      - Tours (Box 138)
      - Trophies, plaques, and medals (Box 138)
      - Union Opera
        - Published photos (Box 138)
        - Unpublished photos (Box 138)
      - Women (Box 138)
      - Women's activities
        - Freshman Pageant, 1929 (Box 138)
        - Lantern Night, 1928 (Box 138)
        - Old English Tea, Martha Cook, 1928 (Box 138)
        - Penny Carnival, 1931 (Box 138)
        - Sophomore Cabaret, 1929; 1936 (Box 138)
        - Sophomore Circus (Box 138)
    - Individuals
      Subjects (Boxes 136-138) primarily includes student and alumni activities at the University, especially sports, reunions, and commencements. This subseries overlaps the University Buildings subseries, which also includes some activities, and the Individuals subseries below, which includes photos of the activities of notable figures at the University. [A detailed name inventory is available in a separate finding aid. See University of Michigan Alumni Association, Individual Photographs.]
      - A-Ai (Box 139)
      - Abbot (Box 139)
      - Adams (Box 139)
      - Africa, Bernabe (Box 139)
      - Ak-Am (Box 139)
      - Allen (Box 139)
      - An-Az (Box 139)
      - Anderson (Box 139)
      - Angell (Box 139)
      - Angell, James B (Box 139)
      - Ba-Bay (Box 139)
      - Bacon (Box 139)
      - Baird (Box 139)
      - Baker (Box 139)
      - Bates (Box 139)
      - Be-Bi (Box 139)
      - Bla-Blu (Box 139)
      - Bm-Bp (Box 139)
      - Bra-Bry (Box 139)
      - Brown (Box 139)
      - Brucker, Wilber M. (Box 139)
      - Buc-Buz (Box 139)
      - Burke, Arleigh (Box 139)
      - Burton, Marion L (Box 139)
      - Ca-Cav (Box 139)
      - Campbell (Box 139)
      - Carver, Harry (Box 139)
      - Ce- (Box 139)
      - Chad-Chan (Box 139)
      - Chamberl(a)in (Box 139)
      - Chandler (Box 139)
      - Chap-Chay (Box 139)
      - Chapin (Box 139)
      - Chapman (Box 139)
      - Chase (Box 139)
      - Che- (Box 139)
      - Chen(g) (Box 139)
      - Chi-Cho (Box 139)
      - Chr- (Box 139)
      - Chu-Ci (Box 139)
      - Clai-Clay (Box 139)
      - Clark(e), A.-Clark(e), D (Box 139)
      - Clark(e), H.-Clark(e), W (Box 139)
      - Cle- (Box 139)
      - Clement(s) (Box 139)
      - Cli-Cm (Box 139)
      - Coa-Coh (Box 139)
      - Cobb (Box 139)
      - Cody (Box 139)
      - Colb-Colg (Box 139)
      - Cole (Box 139)
      - Coll-Colv (Box 139)
      - Collins (Box 139)
      - Com-Cong (Box 139)
      - Comstock (Box 139)
      - Conk-Conw (Box 139)
      - Coo-Cop (Box 139)
      - Cook, A.-Cook, G (Box 139)
      - Cook, H.-Cook, Z (Box 139)
      - Cooper (Box 139)
      - Cora-Cory (Box 139)
      - Cos-Cot (Box 139)
      - Cou-Cow (Box 139)
      - Cox (Box 139)
      - Crab-Craw (Box 139)
      - Crane (Box 139)
      - Crawford (Box 139)
      - Cre-Cri (Box 139)
      - Cro (Box 139)
      - Cross, Crossman (Box 139)
      - Cru-Cum (Box 139)
      - Cun-Cz (Box 139)
      - Curtice, Curtis, Curtiss (Box 139)
      - Dag-Dal (Box 139)
      - Dam-Dan (Box 139)
      - Damon, Norman (Box 139)
      - Danforth (Box 139)
      - Daniels (Box 139)
      - Dar- (Box 139)
      - Darling, Darnall, Darnell (Box 139)
      - David, Davidson, Davies (Box 139)
      - Dau-Daw (Box 139)
      - Davis, A.-Davis, E (Box 139)
      - Davis, F.-Davis, L (Box 139)
      - Davis, M.-Davis, W (Box 139)
      - Dawson (Box 139)
      - Day (Box 139)
      - Dea-Dek (Box 140)
      - Del-Dem (Box 140)
      - Den- (Box 140)
      - Deo-Dev (Box 140)
      - Dew-Dez (Box 140)
      - Dewey (Box 140)
      - Dewey, Thomas E (Box 140)
      - Dia-Die (Box 140)
      - Dickenson (Box 140)
      - Dif-Diz (Box 140)
      - Doa-Dod (Box 140)
      - Doe-Don (Box 140)
      - Donahue, Donaldson (Box 140)
      - Donovan, Dougherty (Box 140)
      - Doo-Doy (Box 140)
      - Douglas(s) (Box 140)
      - Dow (Box 140)
      - Downey, Downing (Box 140)
      - Dr- (Box 140)
      - Drake (Box 140)
      - Drysdale, Taylor (Box 140)
      - Dub-Duf (Box 140)
      - Dug-Dun (Box 140)
      - Dup-Dy (Box 140)
      - Ea- (Box 140)
      - Earle (Box 140)
      - Eb-Ed (Box 140)
      - Edmonson, James B (Box 140)
      - Ee-Eh (Box 140)
      - Ei-Ek (Box 140)
      - Eisenhower (-hauer), Eiserman(n) (Box 140)
      - Elb-Elk (Box 140)
      - Elbel, Louis (Box 140)
      - Ell-Ely (Box 140)
      - Elliot(t) (Box 140)
      - Elliott, Peter (Box 140)
      - Ellis (Box 140)
      - Em-Es (Box 140)
      - Emanuel, Julia E (Box 140)
      - Emery (Box 140)
      - Emmons, Harold (Box 140)
      - Es-Eu (Box 140)
      - Eva- (Box 140)
      - Eve- (Box 140)
      - Ew-Ez (Box 140)
      - Fab-Fal (Box 140)
      - Fairchild (Box 140)
      - Fairman (Box 140)
      - Fan-Far (Box 140)
      - Farmer (Box 140)
      - Farnsworth (Box 140)
      - Farrand (Box 140)
      - Farrell, William R (Box 140)
      - Fas-Fay (Box 140)
      - Fead, Louis H (Box 140)
      - Fed-Fen (Box 140)
      - Fer-Fez (Box 140)
      - Ferguson (Box 140)
      - Field (Box 140)
      - Fif-Fil (Box 140)
      - Fin (Box 140)
      - Fink (Box 140)
      - Fir-Fis (Box 140)
      - Fis(c)her (Box 140)
      - Fisher (Sports: Charles, Ray) (Box 140)
      - Fit-Fix (Box 140)
      - Fitz- (Box 140)
      - Fla-Fli (Box 140)
      - Flem(m)ing (Box 140)
      - Fletcher (Box 140)
      - Flo-Flx (Box 140)
      - Fog-Fon (Box 140)
      - Foo-Forb (Box 140)
      - Ford-Fore (Box 140)
      - Ford, Gerald R (Box 140)
      - Forr-Fors (Box 140)
      - Fos-Fow (Box 140)
      - Foster (Box 140)
      - Fox (Box 140)
      - Frac-Franke (Box 140)
      - Franck, Harry (Box 140)
      - Frankl-Fraz (Box 140)
      - Fred-Frei (Box 140)
      - French-Frey (Box 140)
      - Fri- (Box 140)
      - Friedman (Box 140)
      - Fro-Fry (Box 140)
      - Ful-Fuo (Box 140)
      - Fur-Fut (Box 140)
      - Gab-Gai (Box 141)
      - Galb-Gale (Box 141)
      - Gall-Galv (Box 141)
      - Gan- (Box 141)
      - Garb-Gard (Box 141)
      - Garl-Garv (Box 141)
      - Gas-Gat (Box 141)
      - Gau-Gaw (Box 141)
      - Geb-Ged (Box 141)
      - Gei- (Box 141)
      - Gel-Geo (Box 141)
      - Ger-Gey (Box 141)
      - Gib-Gif (Box 141)
      - Gibson (Box 141)
      - Gilb- (Box 141)
      - Gilc-Gill (Box 141)
      - Gille-Giln (Box 141)
      - Gin-Giz (Box 141)
      - Glad-Glat (Box 141)
      - Glas (Box 141)
      - Gle-Glo (Box 141)
      - Gob-God (Box 141)
      - Goe-Goi (Box 141)
      - Gol-Gon (Box 141)
      - Goldberg, Goldsmith (Box 141)
      - Good(e) (Box 141)
      - Goodell, Goodw- (Box 141)
      - Goodrich (Box 141)
      - Gord-Gorn (Box 141)
      - Gordon (Box 141)
      - Gos-Got (Box 141)
      - Gou-Goy (Box 141)
      - Gould, Goulding (Box 141)
      - Gould, Laurence M (Box 141)
      - Gra-Grad (Box 141)
      - Graf-Grai (Box 141)
      - Gran-Grau (Box 141)
      - Gray (Box 141)
      - Grea-Greenwood (Box 141)
      - Green(e) (Box 141)
      - Green, Fred W (Box 141)
      - Greg-Grei (Box 141)
      - Gren-Grey (Box 141)
      - Grid-Grif (Box 141)
      - Griffin (Box 141)
      - Grig-Griz (Box 141)
      - Grog-Grot (Box 141)
      - Grov-Grow (Box 141)
      - Gru (Box 141)
      - Gua-Gum (Box 141)
      - Guild (Box 141)
      - Gun-Guy (Box 141)
      - Haa- (Box 141)
      - Hac-Haf (Box 141)
      - Hackett (Box 141)
      - Hag- (Box 141)
      - Hah-Hai (Box 141)
      - Haile Selassie (Box 141)
      - Hala-Halz (Box 141)
      - Hall (Box 141)
      - Haller (Box 141)
      - Ham-Hamp (Box 141)
      - Hamilton (Box 141)
      - Hammond (Box 141)
      - Hana-Hanl (Box 141)
      - Hanavan (Box 141)
      - Hann-Hanz (Box 141)
      - Harb-Harg (Box 141)
      - Harl-Harm (Box 141)
      - Harmon, Tom (Box 141)
      - Harn-Harrod (Box 141)
      - Harrigan (Box 141)
      - Harris (Box 141)
      - Harrison (Box 141)
      - Hars-Harv (Box 141)
      - Hart (Box 141)
      - Hartman (Box 141)
      - Has-Hast (Box 141)
      - Hat-Hau (Box 141)
      - Hatch (Box 141)
      - Hatcher, Harlan (Box 141)
      - Hav- (Box 141)
      - Haw-Hawv (Box 141)
      - Hay-Haz (Box 141)
      - Hayde(o)n (Box 141)
      - Hay(e)s (Box 141)
      - Hea-Heb (Box 141)
      - Heath (Box 141)
      - Hec-Hee (Box 141)
      - Hei (Box 141)
      - Hel (Box 141)
      - Hem-Hep (Box 141)
      - Henderson (Box 141)
      - Herbert (Box 141)
      - Herd-Herr (Box 141)
      - Hert-Hes (Box 141)
      - Heston (Box 141)
      - Heu-Hew (Box 141)
      - Hey-Hez (Box 141)
      - Hib-Hig (Box 141)
      - Hila-Hille (Box 141)
      - Hildebran(d)t (Box 141)
      - Hildner (Box 141)
      - Hilkene, Bruce L (Box 141)
      - Hill, A.-Hill, J (Box 141)
      - Hill, L.-Hill, Z (Box 141)
      - Him-Hin (Box 141)
      - Hip-Hiz (Box 141)
      - Hoa-Hoc (Box 142)
      - Hobbs, William Herbert (Box 142)
      - Hod-Hoe (Box 142)
      - Hof-Hold (Box 142)
      - Hof(f)man (Box 142)
      - Holi-Holl (Box 142)
      - Holm-Holz (Box 142)
      - Holmes (Box 142)
      - Hom-Hop (Box 142)
      - Hood (Box 142)
      - Hor- (Box 142)
      - Hos-Hou (Box 142)
      - How-Hoz (Box 142)
      - Howard (Box 142)
      - Howell (Box 142)
      - Hsu-Hue (Box 142)
      - Huber (Box 142)
      - Hudson (Box 142)
      - Huebner, George J., Jr (Box 142)
      - Huf-Hum (Box 142)
      - Hughes (Box 142)
      - Humphrey(s) (Box 142)
      - Hun- (Box 142)
      - Hur- (Box 142)
      - Hus-Hut (Box 142)
      - Hutchins, Harry B (Box 142)
      - Hya-Hyn (Box 142)
      - Hyde (Box 142)
      - Ik-In (Box 142)
      - Ir-Ivy (Box 142)
      - Irv(w)in (Box 142)
      - Jab-Jam (Box 142)
      - Jackson (Box 142)
      - Jacob(son) (Box 142)
      - James (Box 142)
      - Jan-Jay (Box 142)
      - Jef-Jel (Box 142)
      - Jenk-Jens (Box 142)
      - Jennings (Box 142)
      - Jer-Jim (Box 142)
      - Joa-Jonk (Box 142)
      - John, Johnston (Box 142)
      - Johnson, A.-Johnson, H (Box 142)
      - Johnson, I.-Johnson, Z (Box 142)
      - Johnson, Roy W (Box 142)
      - Jones, A.-Jones, E (Box 142)
      - Jones, F.-Jones, M (Box 142)
      - Jones, J. Paul (Box 142)
      - Jones, N.-Jones, Z (Box 142)
      - Jor-Jos (Box 142)
      - Jot-Joyce (Box 142)
      - Ju- (Box 142)
      - Kag-Kal (Box 142)
      - Kam-Kane (Box 142)
      - Kani-Kap (Box 142)
      - Kar-Kas (Box 142)
      - Kat-Kauf (Box 142)
      - Kaul-Kay (Box 142)
      - Kea-Keet (Box 142)
      - Keene, Clifford (Box 142)
      - Kei-Kell (Box 142)
      - Kell(e)y (Box 142)
      - Kellogg (Box 142)
      - Kem-Kenda (Box 142)
      - Kendr-Kent (Box 142)
      - Kendrick, Milton (Box 142)
      - Kennedy (Box 142)
      - Kep-Ker (Box 142)
      - Kes-Key (Box 142)
      - Kh-Kie (Box 142)
      - Kil-Kim (Box 142)
      - Kimball (Box 142)
      - Kinc-King (Box 142)
      - King (Box 142)
      - Kinh-Kino (Box 142)
      - Kip-Kirkb (Box 142)
      - Kipke, Harry (Box 142)
      - Kirke-Kirt (Box 142)
      - Kirw-Kiz (Box 142)
      - Kla-Kle (Box 142)
      - Klein-Kleinst (Box 142)
      - Klim-Klin (Box 142)
      - Klip-Klu (Box 142)
      - Knaf-Knau (Box 142)
      - Kne-Knig (Box 142)
      - Knis-Knot (Box 142)
      - Know-Koc (Box 142)
      - Kod-Koh (Box 142)
      - Kohler (Box 142)
      - Kol-Kon (Box 142)
      - Koo-Kor (Box 142)
      - Kos-Koy (Box 142)
      - Kra-Kri (Box 142)
      - Kramer (Box 142)
      - Kraus, Krause, Krauss (Box 142)
      - Kraus, E. H (Box 142)
      - Kraus, John D (Box 142)
      - Kremer(s) (Box 142)
      - Kresge (Box 142)
      - Kress (Box 142)
      - Kro-Kru (Box 142)
      - Kub-Kuh (Box 142)
      - Kui-Kuz (Box 142)
      - Ky- (Box 142)
      - Lab-Lag (Box 143)
      - Lai-Lam (Box 143)
      - Lamont (Box 143)
      - Lanc-Lane (Box 143)
      - Lang-Lanx (Box 143)
      - Lang, Chester H (Box 143)
      - Laph-Lar (Box 143)
      - Las-Lat (Box 143)
      - Lau-Lav (Box 143)
      - Law-Laz (Box 143)
      - Lawton, J. Fred (Box 143)
      - Lea-Leb (Box 143)
      - Lec-Lee (Box 143)
      - Lef-Leh (L'H) (Box 143)
      - Lei-Lel (Box 143)
      - Lem- (Box 143)
      - Len- (Box 143)
      - Leo-Lep (Box 143)
      - Ler-Les (Box 143)
      - Let-Leve (Box 143)
      - Levi-Ley (Box 143)
      - Levy (Box 143)
      - Lewis, C.-Lewis, J (Box 143)
      - Lewis, M.-Lewis, W (Box 143)
      - Lia-Lif (Box 143)
      - Lichty, George (Box 143)
      - Lig-Lik (Box 143)
      - Lil-Lim (Box 143)
      - Lina-Lindb (Box 143)
      - Linde-Lint (Box 143)
      - Lip-Litc (Box 143)
      - Litt-Litz (Box 143)
      - Little, Clarence Cook (Box 143)
      - Liu-Liv (Box 143)
      - Livingston, Joseph A (Box 143)
      - Lloyd (Box 143)
      - Lo-Loe (Box 143)
      - Lof-Lom (Box 143)
      - Lon- (Box 143)
      - Loo-Lop (Box 143)
      - Lor-Loud (Box 143)
      - Lov-Loy (Box 143)
      - Lub-Lum (Box 143)
      - Lun-Luz (Box 143)
      - Lyd-Lyn (Box 143)
      - Lyo-Lyt (Box 143)
      - Mac (Box 143)
      - M(a)cAf-M(a)cAn (Box 143)
      - M(a)cAr-M(a)cB (Box 143)
      - M(a)cCab-M(a)cCan (Box 143)
      - M(a)cCar-M(a)cCas (Box 143)
      - M(a)cCau-M(a)cCl (Box 143)
      - MacChesney, Nathan William (Box 143)
      - M(a)cCob-M(a)cCon (Box 143)
      - M(a)cCor-M(a)cCow (Box 143)
      - M(a)cCormick, M(a)cCormack (Box 143)
      - M(a)cCoy (Box 143)
      - M(a)cCr-M(a)cCu (Box 143)
      - M(a)cD- (Box 143)
      - M(a)cDonald (Box 143)
      - M(a)cF- (Box 143)
      - M(a)cG- (Box 143)
      - M(a)cH-M(a)cI (Box 143)
      - M(a)cKa-M(a)cKette (Box 143)
      - M(a)cKee (Box 143)
      - M(a)cKenzie (Box 143)
      - McKeye, Caryl (Box 143)
      - M(a)cKh-M(a)cKo (Box 143)
      - M(a)cLa-M(a)cLee (Box 143)
      - M(a)cLaughlin (Box 143)
      - M(a)cLeo-M(a)cMan (Box 143)
      - M(a)cMas-M(a)cMu (Box 143)
      - M(a)cNa-M(a)cNe (Box 143)
      - M(a)cNi-M(a)cP (Box 143)
      - M(a)cR-M(a)cW (Box 143)
      - Mad-Mae (Box 143)
      - Madden (Box 143)
      - Mag-Mah (Box 143)
      - Mai-Mak (Box 143)
      - Mal-Malz (Box 143)
      - Malcolm (Box 143)
      - Manc-Manl (Box 143)
      - Mann-Mano (Box 143)
      - Mans-Map (Box 143)
      - Mara-Mard (Box 143)
      - Mari-Marl (Box 143)
      - Maro-Marz (Box 143)
      - Marsh (Box 143)
      - Marshall (Box 143)
      - Martin, A.-Martin, H (Box 143)
      - Martin, J.-Martin, Z (Box 143)
      - Mas- (Box 143)
      - Mason (Box 143)
      - Mate-Mats (Box 143)
      - Matt-Matz (Box 143)
      - Matthaei, Frederick C., and Frederick C., Jr (Box 143)
      - Mat(t)hews (Box 143)
      - Mau- (Box 143)
      - Max-May (Box 143)
      - Maye-Maz (Box 143)
      - Mea- (Box 144)
      - Meader, George (Box 144)
      - Mec-Mei (Box 144)
      - Mel-Men (Box 144)
      - Melbin, Murray (Box 144)
      - Merc-Merk (Box 144)
      - Merr- (Box 144)
      - Mers-Met (Box 144)
      - Mey- (Box 144)
      - Mic-Mid (Box 144)
      - Michael(s) (Box 144)
      - Mie-Mik (Box 144)
      - Mila-Milr (Box 144)
      - Miller, A.-Miller, C (Box 144)
      - Miller, D.-Miller, G (Box 144)
      - Miller, H (Box 144)
      - Miller, J.-Miller, N (Box 144)
      - Miller, P.-Miller, W (Box 144)
      - Mills (Box 144)
      - Min- (Box 144)
      - Mis-Mit (Box 144)
      - Mitchel(l) (Box 144)
      - Moa-Moi (Box 144)
      - Mol- (Box 144)
      - Mom-Monr (Box 144)
      - Mont- (Box 144)
      - Mood-Moor (Box 144)
      - Moore, A.-Moore, E (Box 144)
      - Moore, F.-Moore, W (Box 144)
      - Mora-More (Box 144)
      - Morg-Mori (Box 144)
      - Morl-Morr (Box 144)
      - Morris (Box 144)
      - Morrison (Box 144)
      - Mors-Mort (Box 144)
      - Morton (Box 144)
      - Mos- (Box 144)
      - Mosher (Box 144)
      - Mot-Mr (Box 144)
      - Mott, Charles S (Box 144)
      - Muc-Mue (Box 144)
      - Muh-Mul (Box 144)
      - Mum-Mun (Box 144)
      - Mur- (Box 144)
      - Murphy, A.-Murphy, I (Box 144)
      - Murphy, J.-Murphy, W (Box 144)
      - Murray (Box 144)
      - Mus-Muz (Box 144)
      - My-Myers (Box 144)
      - Na- (Box 144)
      - Nea-Neg (Box 144)
      - Neh-Nes (Box 144)
      - Nelson, A.-Nelson, G (Box 144)
      - Nelson, J.-Nelson, W (Box 144)
      - Neu- (Box 144)
      - Nev-Newb (Box 144)
      - Newc-Newl (Box 144)
      - Newman (Box 144)
      - Newn-Newt (Box 144)
      - Nic- (Box 144)
      - Nichols-Nicholson (Box 144)
      - Nie-Nix (Box 144)
      - Niehuss, Marvin L (Box 144)
      - Nob-Nol (Box 144)
      - Norc-Norr (Box 144)
      - North (Box 144)
      - Norto-Noy (Box 144)
      - Novy, Frederick G (Box 144)
      - Nu-Ny (Box 144)
      - Oa-Ob (Box 144)
      - O'Brien (Box 144)
      - Oc- (Box 144)
      - Od-Oe (Box 144)
      - Of-Oh (Box 144)
      - Ok-Ol (Box 144)
      - Olse(o)n (Box 144)
      - Om-Op (Box 144)
      - Or- (Box 144)
      - Os- (Box 144)
      - Osborn(e) (Box 144)
      - Osborn, Chase S (Box 144)
      - Ot- (Box 144)
      - Ottaway (Box 144)
      - Ov-Oz (Box 144)
      - Owen(s) (Box 144)
      - Pab-Pai (Box 144)
      - Pal-Paq (Box 144)
      - Palmer, A.-Palmer, M (Box 144)
      - Palmer, N.-Palmer, Z (Box 144)
      - Par- (Box 144)
      - Park(s) (Box 144)
      - Parker (Box 144)
      - Pas-Pat (Box 144)
      - Patten, Pat(t)on (Box 144)
      - Pat(t)erson (Box 144)
      - Pau- (Box 144)
      - Pea- (Box 144)
      - Peak(e) (Box 144)
      - Peare, Robert (Box 144)
      - Pearson (Box 144)
      - Pec-Pee (Box 144)
      - Pei-Pem (Box 144)
      - Pen- (Box 144)
      - Pep-Pes (Box 144)
      - Perkins (Box 144)
      - Perrin(g) (Box 144)
      - Perry (Box 144)
      - Pet-Pez (Box 144)
      - Peterso(e)n (Box 144)
      - Petosky (Box 144)
      - Pf-Ph (Box 145)
      - Phillips (Box 145)
      - Phillips, Ulrich Bonnell (Box 145)
      - Pia-Pie (Box 145)
      - Pierce (Box 145)
      - Pil-Pim (Box 145)
      - Pip-Piz (Box 145)
      - Pla-Plu (Box 145)
      - Pod-Pol (Box 145)
      - Pollo(a)ck (Box 145)
      - Pom-Pop (Box 145)
      - Pond (Box 145)
      - Por-Pot (Box 145)
      - Porter (Box 145)
      - Potter (Box 145)
      - Pou-Poz (Box 145)
      - Pound, Arthur (Box 145)
      - Power(s) (Box 145)
      - Pra-Pre (Box 145)
      - Pratt (Box 145)
      - Prentiss (Box 145)
      - Pri- (Box 145)
      - Price (Box 145)
      - Pro-Pry (Box 145)
      - Pryor, Millard (Box 145)
      - Pt-Pu (Box 145)
      - Rab-Raf (Box 145)
      - Rah-Ran (Box 145)
      - Rap-Rat (Box 145)
      - Rav-Raz (Box 145)
      - Rea-Red (Box 145)
      - Reec-Reev (Box 145)
      - Reed (Box 145)
      - Reg-Reic (Box 145)
      - Reid (Box 145)
      - Reif-Reis (Box 145)
      - Rem-Ren (Box 145)
      - Res-Rey (Box 145)
      - Revelli (Box 145)
      - Rh- (Box 145)
      - Rice-Richards (Box 145)
      - Richardson (Box 145)
      - Richart-Rickey (Box 145)
      - Rid-Rig (Box 145)
      - Ril-Rin (Box 145)
      - Rio-Riv (Box 145)
      - Roa-Roc (Box 145)
      - Rob(b)ins (Box 145)
      - Roberts (Box 145)
      - Robertson (Box 145)
      - Robinson (Box 145)
      - Rod- (Box 145)
      - Roe- (Box 145)
      - Rog-Ron (Box 145)
      - Rogers (Box 145)
      - Roo-Rop (Box 145)
      - Roosevelt, Eleanor (Box 145)
      - Rosa-Rosen (Box 145)
      - Roser-Rot (Box 145)
      - Ross (Box 145)
      - Rou-Rowen (Box 145)
      - Rowl-Roy (Box 145)
      - Rub-Rum (Box 145)
      - Run-Ruz (Box 145)
      - Russell (Box 145)
      - Ruthven, Alexander Grant
        - Portraits and singles (Box 145)
        - With family and horse (Box 145)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 145)
      - Ry- (Box 145)
      - Saa-Sac (Box 145)
      - Sad-St. Peter (Box 145)
      - Sak-Sam (Box 145)
      - San- (Box 145)
      - Sanders (Box 145)
      - Sar-Sau (Box 145)
      - Sav-Say (Box 145)
      - Sawyer, Ralph A (Box 145)
      - Sca-Scha (Box 146)
      - Schaef(f)er (Box 146)
      - Sche-Schi (Box 146)
      - Schl- (Box 146)
      - Schm-Schn (Box 146)
      - Schmidt (Box 146)
      - Scho- (Box 146)
      - Schr- (Box 146)
      - Schub-Schum (Box 146)
      - Schur-Schw (Box 146)
      - Sci-Scr (Box 146)
      - Scott, A.-Scott, J (Box 146)
      - Scott, K.-Scott, W (Box 146)
      - Sea-Sec (Box 146)
      - Seaver, Jay J (Box 146)
      - See-Sen (Box 146)
      - Ser-Sey (Box 146)
      - Sh-Sig (Box 146)
      - Sik-Simm (Box 146)
      - Simon(s) (Box 146)
      - Simo-Sims (Box 146)
      - Sin-Siz (Box 146)
      - Sink, Charles A (Box 146)
      - Sj-Sla (Box 146)
      - Sle-Sly (Box 146)
      - Sma-Smth (Box 146)
      - Smith, A.-Smith, B (Box 146)
      - Smith, C.-Smith(s), F (Box 146)
      - Smith, G.-Smith, H (Box 146)
      - Smith, I.-Smith, N (Box 146)
      - Smith, R.-Smith, S (Box 146)
      - Smith, Shirley W (Box 146)
      - Smith, T.-Smith, Z (Box 146)
      - Sne-Snod (Box 146)
      - Snow-Sny (Box 146)
      - Sob-Som (Box 146)
      - Son-Sou (Box 146)
      - Spa- (Box 146)
      - Spe- (Box 146)
      - Spi- (Box 146)
      - Spr-Spu (Box 146)
      - Sq-Stag (Box 146)
      - Stah-Stan (Box 146)
      - Star-Stay (Box 146)
      - Stea-Stee (Box 146)
      - Stef-Stei (Box 146)
      - Stek-Stet (Box 146)
      - Stevens, Stevenson (Box 146)
      - Stevenson, Russell (Box 146)
      - Steward, Stewart (Box 146)
      - Sti- (Box 146)
      - Stoc-Stok (Box 146)
      - Stol-Stow (Box 146)
      - Stone (Box 146)
      - Stra-Stre (Box 146)
      - Stri-Stry (Box 146)
      - Stu- (Box 146)
      - Sud-Sum (Box 146)
      - Sun- (Box 146)
      - Sup-Sut (Box 146)
      - Swa- (Box 146)
      - Swanson (Box 146)
      - Swe-Swi (Box 146)
      - Swo-Sz (Box 146)
      - Taf-Tan (Box 146)
      - Tap-Tav (Box 146)
      - Tapping, T. Hawley
        - Retirement furlough (Box 146)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 146)
      - Taylor, A.-Taylor, J (Box 146)
      - Taylor, L.-Taylor, W (Box 146)
      - Tea-Tem (Box 146)
      - Ten-Tex (Box 146)
      - Tha-Thi (Box 146)
      - Tho-Thu (Box 146)
      - Thomas, A.-Thomas, E (Box 146)
      - Thomas, J.-Thomas, W (Box 146)
      - Thom(p)son, A.-Thom(p)son, F (Box 146)
      - Thom(p)son, G.-Thom(p)son, W (Box 146)
      - Tib-Til (Box 147)
      - Tim-Tin (Box 147)
      - Tip-Tit (Box 147)
      - Tob-Tol (Box 147)
      - Tom-Ton (Box 147)
      - Too-Toy (Box 147)
      - Townsend (Box 147)
      - Tra- (Box 147)
      - Tre-Tri (Box 147)
      - Tro-Try (Box 147)
      - Tuc-Ty (Box 147)
      - U-Ul (Box 147)
      - Un-Ut (Box 147)
      - Vai-Van Den (Box 147)
      - Vandenberg, Mr. and Mrs. Arthur H (Box 147)
      - Van Der-Van Dy (Box 147)
      - Van E-Van P (Box 147)
      - Van S-Van V (Box 147)
      - Van W-Vaz (Box 147)
      - Ve- (Box 147)
      - Vi- (Box 147)
      - Vo-Vy (Box 147)
      - Wac-Wak (Box 147)
      - Wagner (Box 147)
      - Wala-Wall (Box 147)
      - Walker (Box 147)
      - Wallace (Box 147)
      - Wallace, Mike (Box 147)
      - Walm-Walz (Box 147)
      - Wan-Wart (Box 147)
      - Ward (Box 147)
      - Warner, Warren (Box 147)
      - Was-Waterm (Box 147)
      - Waters-Way (Box 147)
      - Watkins (Box 147)
      - Watson (Box 147)
      - Wea- (Box 147)
      - Web- (Box 147)
      - Wec-Weil (Box 147)
      - Weim-Weis (Box 147)
      - Wel-Wenl (Box 147)
      - Wells (Box 147)